viloud.tv 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy - Viloud

Last uptdated: May, 2018.​

Viloud​ (“Noise Media S.L.”, “us”, “we”, or “our”) is an online video software company. Our primary offerings are a video player and a video content management system.

Viloud complies with the General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR (EU) 2016/679, in force since 25 May 2018. This regulation introduces a number of changes to ensure data protection in the context of the European Union. Our users can trust that their data is managed in a secure environment.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we collect from and about you when you use Viloud’s web-based application (the “Service”). This page also explains how information is collected and used in connection with our corporate website located at [https://viloud.tv](https://viloud.tv/) (the “Website”).

**1\. What information do we collect?**

We collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name and email address, when you voluntarily provide it by registering with us or using the Service. Once you become a user, you may provide additional information in your profile section. Providing additional information is optional. Your user name, email address and any optional profile information that you elect to associate with your account is referred to herein as your “Personal Information.”

If you are a user of our paid premium services, we will utilize a third party credit card payment processing company to collect payment information, including your credit card number, billing address. We will share this payment information with the third party processing company. We do not store your payment information.

**2\. What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To send regular email updates regarding new features that may be of interest to you.

**3\. Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**4\. Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**5\. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. The company may, however, share personally identifiable information with trusted third-party partners. These third party contractors are prohibited from using the information for purposes other than performing services for Viloud.

We may release your information only when we are forced by law, to enforce our site policies, or to protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**6\. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information**

If you would like we update, correct, delete, or deactivate any account information that you have provided us, please send your request to [info@viloud.com](mailto:info@viloud.com), and the company will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt.

**7\. Data Retention Period**

The personal data provided by users to Viloud will be kept for the contractual period, i.e. as long as the user maintains the account active.

**8\. Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information, both during transmission and once it is received. This includes but is not limited to the use of firewalls and encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure; therefore, while the company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.

**9\. Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Noise Media S.L. ​may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**10\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@viloud.com](mailto:info@viloud.com).
